Guide to the Willard Straight Hall records, 1925-2004.
Willard Straight Hall records
- Series XXIV. Alphabetical Subject Files 1946-47
  - General Correspondence Y, 1946-47 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Series XXV. Willard Straight Correspondence 1940's and 1950's
  - Inventory, 1952-56 (Box 31, Folder 42)
  - Expense Distribution, 1942-50 (Box 31, Folder 43)
  - Inventory, 1947 (Box 31, Folder 44)
  - Inventory, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence A, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Activities, Willard Straight Hall, 1948-48 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - General Correspondence B, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - General Correspondence C, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - General Correspondence D, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence E, 1947-49, 56 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence F, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence G, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence H, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence I, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence J, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - General Correspondence K, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - General Correspondence L, 1947-49 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - General Correspondence M, 1947-49, 55 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - General Correspondence N, 1947-58 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - General Correspondence O, 1947-58 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - General Correspondence P, 1947-58 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence R, 1947-58 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - General Correspondence S, 1956-58 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence T, 1947-58 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - General Correspondence V, 1947-57 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - General Correspondence W, 1948-56 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - General Correspondence XYZ, 1947-58 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - General Correspondence K, 1949-51 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - WSH Charges, 1945-56 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Memberships, 1948 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  - Party Set-up forms, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 28)
  - Party Set-up forms, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  - Party Set-up forms, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  - General Correspondence F, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  - W.S. House Department Budgets, 1943-53 (Box 32, Folder 32)
  - General Correspondence N, 1951-55 (Box 32, Folder 33)
  - General Correspondence Q, 1947-57 (Box 32, Folder 34)
  - Room Inventory and Registration, 1955 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  - Repair and Alteration Fund, 1952-54 (Box 32, Folder 36)
  - WSH Budget, 1953-55 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  - WSH Expenses, 1954-55 (Box 32, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Society of Hotelmen, 1955-56 (Box 32, Folder 39)
  - Student Activities, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 40)
  - General Correspondence A, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 41)
  - General Correspondence B, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 42)
  - General Correspondence C, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 43)
  - General Correspondence D, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 44)
  - General Correspondence E, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 45)
  - General Correspondence F, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 46)
  - General Correspondence G, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 47)
  - General Correspondence H, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 48)
  - General Correspondence W, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 49)
  - Alpha Tau Omega, 1956-58 (Box 32, Folder 50)
  - Financial Records, 1956-60 (Box 32, Folder 51)
  - Union Reservations, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 52)
  - Financial Records, 1957-58 (Box 32, Folder 53)
  - General Correspondence G, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 54)
  - Hotel Correspondence, 1958 (Box 32, Folder 55)
  - General Correspondence S, 1957 (Box 32, Folder 56)
- Series XXVI. Financial Data 1925-44
  - Financial Reports, 1925-26 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Financial Reports, 1926-27 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports, 1927-28 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Financial Reports, 1928-29 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Financial Report, 1929-30 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Financial Report, 1930-31 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Financial Reports, 1931-32 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Financial Reports, 1932-33 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Financial Reports, 1933-34 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Financial Report, 1934-35 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Financial Report, 1935-36 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Financial Report, 1936-37 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Financial Reports, 1937-38 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Financial Statements, 1938-39 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Financial Statement, 1939-40 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Financial Statements, 1940-41 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Financial Statement, 1941-42 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Financial Statements, 1942-43 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Financial Statements, 1943-44 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Payroll, 1941-43 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Payroll, 1941-43 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Payrolls, 1943-44 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers, 1945 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Series XXVII. Budget Data 1927-46
  - Budget Data, 1926-27 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Budget Data, 1927-28 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Budget Data, 1928-29 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Budget Data, 1928-29 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Budget Data, 1929-30 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Budget Data, 1930-31 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Budget Data, 1931-32 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Budget Data, 1932-33 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Budget Data, 1933-34 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Budget Data, 1934-35 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Budget Data, 1935-36 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Budget Data, 1936-37 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Budget Data, 1937-38 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Budget Data, 1938-39 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Budget Data, 1939-40 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Budget Data, 1940-41 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Budget Data, 1941-42 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Budget Data, 1942-43 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Budget Data, 1943-44 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Budget Data, 1944-45 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Budget Data, 1944-45 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Budget FMC, 1945-46 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Budget DKP, 1945-46 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1946-47 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Series XXVIII. Willard Straight Items of Interest
  - Elmhirst and Straight, 1920-50 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Emlhirst and Straight, 1920-60 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Willard Straight Student Union, 1915-20 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - WS Student Union Financial Estimates, 1920's (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - WS Student Union letters, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, 1925-60 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Foster Coffin Clippings, 1925-59 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - WS Union Budget Estimate, 1926-27 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - WS Union Proposed Budget, 1932-33 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Browsing Library, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - WS Hall 15th Anniversary, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Speeches, 1940's (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Daily Sun Clippings, 1942-43 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Straight Notes, 1948-49 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - 25th Anniversary, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - WSH Publicity Personal File, 1950, 1984-1985 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - WSH 30th Anniversary, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Photos, 1942-57 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - WSH Newspaper Clippings, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Proposed Addition, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - WSH Info and Reports, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Recruiting, 1983 (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - WSH Activities Photos, Undated (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Kerr Correspondence, 1955-58 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Straight Family Photos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - WSH Administrative Board, Michele Fliegel, 1983 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - WSH in the news, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - NYU Award to F.M. Coffin, 1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Remodeling, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Foster M Coffin, WSH, 1957-60 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - General Correspondence, 1957-60 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Taylor Mali, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Michael Straight, 1957-58 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Unions, 1950's (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Michael Straight, 1950's (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Tompkins County Trust Company, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Allport Correspondence, 1955 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Misc. WSH info, 1959-60 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Art Collection, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Christmas Party, 1925 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Christmas Photos, donated by Robert Hutchins '56, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Dramatic Club, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - WSH Photos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - WSH Photos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - WSH Photos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - WSH Photos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - WSH Photos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - WSH Photos, Undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
- Series XXIX. Oversize Albums and Memorabilia
  - Signatures of People attending various programs, 1938-43 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Film, Campus on the March, Undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook of the Straight, 1949-50 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Historical Photos, 1939-40 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Photos and Covers, 1950-51 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - WSH Employee Photo, Undated (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - WSH Terrace Renovations, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Browsing Library - Photos of WSH, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Photos of WSH, 1960's (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Photos, Undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Photos, Undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Misc Program Activities, 1930-70 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Daily Sun Articles, 1952-53 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook of WSH, 1947-51 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook of WSH, 1958-59 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook of WSH, 1954-55 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Albums, 1940-50's (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - WSH Activities, 1927-35 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - WSH Articles, 1928-30 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - The Veterans, 1950's (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - WSH Publicity Committee Scrapbooks
    - First Years of the Straight, 1923-27 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Publicity Committee Scrapbook, 1943-44 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Publicity Committee Scrapbook, 1945-46 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Publicity Committee Scrapbook, 1946-47 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Publicity Committee Scrapbook, 1950-51 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Publicity Committee Scrapbook, 1951-52 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Publicity Committee Scrapbook, 1963-64 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Publicity Committee Scrapbook, 1967-68 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Noyes Game Room, 1958-67 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Kimball room renovation, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Lamps and lighting, 1960's (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Stair treads, Corridor mats, etc., 1958-61 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Table tops, refurbishing specifications, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Tenants Report, 1956-57, 60-61 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Terrace Lounge, 1960 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Theatre, 1960-64 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Theatre lighting, 1960's (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Theatre, 1960-61 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Theatre, 1926-51 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Photos, 1950's (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - WSH Pamphlets, 1950-55 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - WSH Plans, 1926 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - WSH Photos, 1950's (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Duplicates, 30th Anniversary, 1955 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - WSH Photos, 1950's (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - WSH Photos, 1960's (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - WSH Photos, 1940-60's (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - WSH Photos, 1930's (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Daily Sun, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Cornell Sun Clippings, Summer Term, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - WSH Committee, 1950-60 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - WSH Pamphlets, 1961 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - WSH Photos, 1940-60's (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - WSH Photos, 1950-60's (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - WSH Pamphlets and Magazines, 1950-60 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - WSH Opening, 1924-25 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - General, 1960's (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - General, 1940's (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Music Room Renovations, 1958-63 (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Music Room, 1960's (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Noyes Ground Floor Project, 1960-61 (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Noyes Lodge, 1958-59 (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - International Lounge Project, 1962 (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Ivy Room Terrace, 1958-60 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Bowling Alley, 1958-60 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Barbershop Survey, 1962-63, 68 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Buildings and Reports, 1960-63 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Building Charges, 1960-61 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Art Lounge Renovations, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Activities Corridor, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - International Lounge, 1963-64 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Elmhirst Room Renovation, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Activities Corridor meeting rooms, lofts, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Browsing Library, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Additions to WSH, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - The Journal - Royal Architecture Institute of Canada, 1925 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Photos, 1950's (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Copy of "Davy", Undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Straight News Notebooks, 1941-42, 1946-47 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Straight News Notebooks, 1939-40, 40-41, 42-43 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Straight News Notebook and Record of Oars, 1947-48 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Presentation "This is Cornell", Circa 1960 (Box 35)
    35 mm slides
  - Photos of the Straight and campus, Circa 1920s (Box 35)
    On glass slides
  - WSH Scrapbook, 1952-53 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Photos, Undated (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1953-55 (Box 43, Folder 3)